{
    "id": "c46ee60be5304433b1a04a1244c784a3",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t worry about the work. I will attend …………………. it tomorrow.",
            "description": "To attend to work is to do it. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody paid any attention …………………….. the warning.",
            "description": "People pay attention to something and shower attentions on people.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The young man showered his attentions …………………… his fiancée.",
            "description": "People pay attention to something and shower attentions on people.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Your attendance ……………………. the club meeting is necessary.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The queen was always surrounded ………………………… her attendants.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Alexander Graham Bell astounded the world …………………….. his invention of the telephone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy was so attached …………………… the new puppy that he refused to leave it.",
            "description": "Attach is used with to.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ashamed ………………………… his bad manners.",
            "description": "Ashamed is used with of.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The majority assented ……………………. my views on the matter.",
            "description": "Assent is used with to.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A locker was assigned ……………………….. each student.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was anxious ………………………. her mother’s illness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "about",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Someday his antisocial behavior will land him ……………………… jail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}